http://www.hinkyimport.com/privacy-policy/

Loading... Please wait...
Follow us on:
Sign in or Create an account
Toll Free No.
Newsletter
How To Use A Singing BowlNew EarringsOm Symbol Tibetan JewelryPrayer Beads, a SummaryThe Art of Making Lokta PaperThe Mandala SetTibetan Buddhist ArtTibetan Buddhist Prayer Flags, Uses and MeaningsTibetan Singing Bowls in MeditationChina BooksPhurba Dagger- The Tibetan Buddhist Ritual InstrumentThe Kalachakra Tantra and MantraWho is the Chinese Happy Buddha?Tibetan Buddhist MeditationThe Connection Between Buddhism and WisdomGuan YinGuan Yin Buddha in Chinese Buddhism
View Cart
Our Categories
Tibetan Singing Bowls
Hand-Hammered Singing Bowls
Black Singing Bowls
Blue and Purple Singing Bowls
Green Singing Bowls
Red Singing Bowls
Privacy Policy
Hinkyimport.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for our Web site.
Information Automatically Logged
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. The information collected is used to identify visitor trends and to tailor our site to best suit the needs of our users.
Cookies
Our site does not use cookies.
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. All information collected is sent through SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption. Credit Card information is only used to charge our customers for the products and services they purchase from us. We do not retain credit card information.
Notification of Changes If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If, however, we are going to use users’ personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days.
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: admin@hinkyimport.com or call 1-866-446-5988
About Us
Who are we?
© 2020 Hinkyimport.com. All rights reserved.
